you seem to be critiquing what you think
I'm saying instead of what I'm actually
saying that's what I'm saying that
Twitter is not the best source of with
their like character limit and the way
you can even like have a thread when
you're responding to someone it doesn't
work doesn't work to have a conversation
so I get what your issues are I have an
issue with capitalism that's why I don't
want it to exist on this planet I agree
with dismantling capitalism I don't
think that the way to do that is to make
capitalism greener to put band-aids on
capitalism the only option is to
dismantle it to create a system that is
not in benefit of the tiny 1% where you
get to pass off all of your risks to
humanity and get all of the profit for
yourself but nobody I know has a
solution to actually get there except
for what I am proposing which is that we
create a global tech cooperative so that
we are the ones in control of the tech
company that we utilize because
currently on this planet tech companies
have a lot of power Google and Facebook
with the data we've given them have a
lot more power than even the United
States in some ways they alter elections
they get to bankrupt other companies or
buy them out and either choose to have
that on the market or not they control
our data and control what access we have
to information they are powerful so why
don't we retain that why don't we create
that that we want to use we don't need
to convince I bring one else is using
Google and Facebook we only need a small
group of people enough to make it a
usable threshold and if you create for
that small group of people with their
input and with them being members them
financing it then getting to be to
decide from the ground up how we have
governance how we have how we trust it a
smaller group of people to run it for us
because it's going to be more efficient
to have a board of directors run it for
us but we don't want a board of
directors acting like Google and
Facebook already do and working against
our best interest on the planet so tech
companies have power so we're going to
utilize a tech company in order to
harness our collective power at the same
time
it is only a tech company it does not
control your life it you get to bring to
it what you choose to bring to it so if
we create a system to use your data to
cure cancer you're in control of your
data you get to choose whether or not
you give it the only way you're gonna
give it is if it's if it's voluntary and
safe and so we have to create systems to
make it more and more easy for people to
collaborate at no point are we forcing
people we have to just keep asking how
can we get you to do what we want what
would be in the greater good not you
have to do what's in the greater good
that is hierarchy down and we can't do
it I mean I don't know what you're
proposing because most of what I know is
somebody deciding this is how the world
should work and we're gonna force it to
work that way even in anarchy yes maybe
especially in anarchy and so to be able
to create a world that works for
everybody we don't actually need to take
over a nation because if we took over a
nation do we do then do you know how to
run an economy do you know how to do any
of it our politicians don't even know so
what I'm proposing is we create it with
the scaffolding within our current
capitalist system so that we can
dismantle it because currently if it
went away tomorrow we don't have food in
the supermarkets and people starve we
have chaos and violence and I don't want
chaos and violence so I want to create a
system that works from within the
current one with a tech company at the
same time it is only a tech company it's
not gonna tell you how many children you
can have it's not going to tell you
where you can live and how you can live
and it's not gonna be able to pass laws
all it can which are current ones doo
doo Google a Facebook get to get to
lobby and basically pass laws but
they're not transparent about it
we can be transparent about it we can
create systems to take back our actual
democracies easily for the hands of in
the hands of the people who are the
voters in that democracy we can use our
tech company to take back our economics
to have access to the information on the
products we buy to know-how whether it's
in alignment with our values not you
have to have my values we can create it
so that it doesn't matter what your
values are these products are in
alignment and how could we create
products that are healthy and good for
the environment and have
social impact because that's what we
want to create together as humanity at
no point do you have to do any of it you
don't have to work for anyone you don't
have a boss I don't want a boss I don't
want to be anybody's boss I want to
create a world where I have complete
autonomy over my own life and in order
to do that I need to create a world that
everybody has complete autonomy over
their own life and together we can
co-create the systems for food for
clothing for transportation for energy
for all of it because we bring our minds
together somebody knows how to do that
and when we decide and it doesn't mean
there's gonna be one food system and one
transportation system because who wants
that it means that like we have the
efficiency of one food system but the
choice of many different options so you
can choose which part your your which
system you're a part of which system has
based on what what resources you have to
put in to be part of that system which
one do you want to be a part of and if
none of them work for you how can we
help you create one that does work for
you all we are creating is a tech
company at the same time a tech company
is a very powerful force right now on
this planet